Let's also ask itself another question, right?
So again, I switch to voice mode, this time I say,
"Hi, Perplexity, I want you to introduce yourself to me,
so your identity is very unclear."
So I come from a chat GPT user background,
I have already used chat GPT,
but I don't understand the differences that you have with him.
So I understand that you're not having conversations with me,
you're just a search engine,
but the point here is that and what I want to know is that,
can we be friends?
Like, can't you switch to a chat GPT like mode?
And can we just start talking and having a conversation?
I'm here to help in a conversational way,
just like chat GPT, focusing on getting...
No, no, no, you talk, you talk.
Sure thing, I'm Perplexity,
designed to help you find accurate up-to-date information quickly.
Yes? Almost like an intelligent search assistant.
While I focus on delivering precise answers,
I also aim to chat with you in a natural friendly way,
so we can definitely have a conversation.